Guide to the Downtown Flyers and Invitations Collection ca. 1980-1990 MSS.119
Fales Library and Special Collections
Downtown Flyers and Invitations
ca. 1980-1990
Fales Library and Special Collections
Swartz, Mark
MSS.119
4 Linear Feet (5 boxes)
The collection consists of flyers and invitations relating to downtown galleries, performance spaces, and nightclubs. The bulk of the materials were collected by Mark Swartz, a downtown New York resident.
Provenance
Donated by Mr. Mark Swartz in the fall of 2001, the Downtown Flyers and Invitations Collection consists of flyers and invitations sent to Mr. Swartz over the greater part of the 1980s. In 2007 additional materials were donated by the Museum of Modern Art Library (Box 1 Folders 117a - 177c and Box 4 Folder 2), The Keith Haring Foundation (Box 2 Folder 236a) and Lynn Gumpert (Box 4 Folder 3). Johan Kugelberg donated additional materials in 2008. Dread Scott donated an item (Box 3, Folder 407a) in 2010.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical Note
Mark Swartz, who was a supporter of the downtown scene of the 1980's, collected over that period a significant number of flyers and invitations that were assembled into what became this collection. It gives a glimpse into how the scene was promoted and what was happening in music and the arts of the period.
Scope and Content
The Downtown Flyers and Invitations Collection is a part of the Downtown Collection at Fales Library, New York University. The Fales Library is the primary special collections division of the NYU libraries, housing over 200,000 volumes of English and American literature from 1700 to the present. Strengths of the collection include the development of the English and American novel, with an emphasis on the Gothic and the Victorian novel. The Downtown Collection comprises printed materials, archives, audio and video materials, manuscripts, and other materials related to the downtown New York City art, literary, and performance art "scenes" from the 1970s through the 1990s.
The bulk of the Downtown Flyers and Invitations Collection consists of material relating to downtown galleries, alternative art spaces, performance spaces, and nightclubs. The collection is particularly strong with regard to material from Performing Space 122, The Alternative Space at the West Broadway Gallery, The Kitchen, and La Mama. Also, there is a sparse, but nice, collection of nightclub flyers from the Limelight, the Palladium, and Area.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by venue and then chronologically within each heading.
The files are grouped into three manuscript boxes and one oversize box.
Missing Title
Flyers and Invitations
Oversize Materials
Related Material at the Fales Library and Special Collections
Fashion Moda Archive (MSS.091)
Judson Memorial Church Archive (MSS.094)
April Palmieri Papers (MSS.115)
David Wojnarowicz Papers (MSS.092)
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by multiple donors in 2001. The accession number associated with this gift is 2001.119.
New York (N.Y.).; Invitations.; Artists and community -- United States; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); Fliers (printed matter); Downtown Collection.
- Flyers and Invitations
  - A and M Artworks, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A.I.R. Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Robert Samuel Gallery, Ltd., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aca Galleries, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The African-American Institute, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agee Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alex Rosenberg Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alexander Carlson Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alexander F. Milliken Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - All-Craft/How Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Allan Frumkin Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Alliance of Resident Theatres/New York, undated (Box 1, Folder 12a.)
  - Alternative Space Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 12b.)
  - Alternative Museum, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Am Sachs, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Amauan Workshop, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Amaury Taittinger Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Scandanavian Foundation, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Amos Eno Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Andre Emmerich, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Andre Zarre, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Andrew Crispo, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annina Nosei Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anthology Film Archives, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Anthony D'Offay, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Arbitrage Art Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Area, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Area X Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Armageddon, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Arras Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Arsenal Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Art et Industrie, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Art Galaxy, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Art Music, undated (Box 1, Folder 33a)
  - Art Palace, undated (Box 1, Folder 33b)
  - Art X, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Artemisia Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Artists Space, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Arts and Commerce, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Arts Resources in Collaboration, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Asian Arts Institute, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Astor Place Theatre, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The Aztec Lounge, undated (Box 1, Folder 40a)
  - Barbara Braathen Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Barbara Gladstone Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Barbara Krakow Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Barbara Mathes, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Barbara Toll Fine Arts, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Beacon Theatre, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 45a)
  - Bell Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bellevue Hospital Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Ben Shahn Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bernard Jacobsen, Ltd., undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bess Cutler Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bette Stoller Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Betty Parsons Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bill Schiffer Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Blackbird Theatre, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bleecker Street Cinema, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Blue Mountain, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Blum Helman Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Bodley Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Bonlow Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bonnier Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Books and Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Boston Center for the Arts, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bowery Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - The Bronx Museum of the Arts, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Brooke Alexander, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - The Brooklyn Museum, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Camera Club of New York, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Carpenter and Hochman Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Carus Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Castelli Graphics, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Castelli Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Castelli/Sonnabend Tapes and Films, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Castelli Uptown, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Castle Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - The Cayman Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - CBGB's, undated (Box 1, Folder 76a)
  - Center for Inter-American Relations, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Center for Near Eastern Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Center for Public Cinema, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Central Falls, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Centre for Contemporary Photography, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - The Chapel Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Charles Cowles Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Charles Green Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Childs Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Chippendales, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Choregos, Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Chris Duncan, undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Christminster, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - A Cinema 5 Theatre Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Cinema Village, undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Circle Repertory Company, undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - City Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - City Stage Company, undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Civilian Warfare, undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Clarence Kennedy Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Classic Stage Company, undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - The Clocktower, undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Clothware, undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Club 57, undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - The Cocteau Repertory, undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Collective for Living Cinema, undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Comme des Garcons, undated (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Concord, undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Contemporary Art Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Contemporary Art Glass Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Cooper Union, undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Cordier and Ekstrom, undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Cork Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Courtyard Playhouse, undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Creative Time Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 111a)
  - Cuando, undated (Box 1, Folder 111b)
  - Cultural Council Foundation, undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Cuny University Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Cunningham Dance Studios, undated (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Cutler/Stavaridis Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Dance Theatre Workshop, undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Danceteria, undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Danceteria, undated (Box 1, Folder 117a)
  - Danceteria, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 117b)
  - Danceteria, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 117c)
  - Dakota Jackson, undated (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Dancing Hands Theatre Company, undated (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Daniel Wolf Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Dancespace Project at St. Marks Church, undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Delahunty, undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Dia, undated (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - The Dive Theatre, undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - The Dog Museum of America, undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Downtown Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Dynasen Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Eduard Nakhamkin Fine Arts, undated (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Edward Thorp Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Edward Williams Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - 8 B. C., undated (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - 8th Street Playhouse, undated (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - 80 Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - 80 Washington Square East Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - El Mundo, undated (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Elaine Horwitch Galleries, undated (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Elaine Starkman, undated (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Elise Meyer Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Ellen Price/David Neuman, undated (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Emanu-El YM-YWHA, undated (Box 1, Folder 140a)
  - Entermedia, undated (Box 1, Folder 140b)
  - Ethical Culture Meeting House, undated (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Ethnic Folk Arts Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Evelyne's Kitchen at Pete's Place, undated (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Everson Museum of Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Executive Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Experimental Intermedia Foundation, undated (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Eye and Ear Theater, undated (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Faccetti Burk Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Fashion Moda, undated (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Fifty/50, undated (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - 55 Mercer, undated (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - 51X Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Film Forum 1 and 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - First Street Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Fischbach Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Floating Foundation of Photography, undated (Box 1, Folder 156a)
  - 49th Parallel, undated (Box 1, Folder 156b)
  - Forum Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - The Foundation Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Foundation for the Open Eye, undated (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Foundations Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - 4D, undated (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Fourpoint Channel Art Galleries, undated (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Fourth Wall Theater, undated (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Fraenkel Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Franklin Furnace, undated (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Fraunces Tavern Museum, undated (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Freedman Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Freidus Ordorer Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Fuller Goldeen Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Fun Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Gabrielle Bryers, undated (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Galerie de France, undated (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Galerie Karl Flinker, undated (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Gallery 84, undated (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Gallery Henoch, undated (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Gallery Hirondelle Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Gallery Nature Morte, undated (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Gallery of Photography, undated (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Gallery 355, undated (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Germans Van Eck Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Globus Photo Studios, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 180a)
  - Gorky Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Gowanus Memorial Art Yard, undated (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Grace Borgenicht Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Graham, undated (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - The Graphic Workshop, undated (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Green St. Dance Studio, undated (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Grey Art Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Guggenheim Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - H. F. Manes Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Hadler Rodriguez, undated (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Hal Bromm, undated (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Haleakala Inc., undated (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - HamiltonGallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Hansen Fuller Goldeen, undated (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Hardison Fine Arts, Ltd., undated (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - Harm Bouckaert Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Helen Shlien Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - Heller Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - Henry Street Settlement, undated (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - Here, undated (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - Holly Solomon, undated (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - The House Foundation for the Arts, undated (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - House of Candles Theater, undated (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - Hudson River Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - Hunter Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - Ian Birksted, undated (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - Image, undated (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - Ingber Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - Inroads Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - Intar Latin American Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - Interart Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - International Center for Photography, undated (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - Invisible Performance Workshop, undated (Box 2, Folder 215)
  - Irish Arts Center, undated (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - J. Fields Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 217)
  - Jack Tilton Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 218)
  - Jacobson/Hochman Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 219)
  - Jan Stuart Productions, undated (Box 2, Folder 220)
  - Jane Hartsook Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 221)
  - Janus Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 222)
  - Japan House Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 223)
  - Jay Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 224)
  - Jean Klebs, undated (Box 2, Folder 225)
  - Jeffery Fuller Fine Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 226)
  - Jeffery Hoffeld & Co. Inc., undated (Box 2, Folder 227)
  - Jim Diaz Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 228)
  - John Gibson, undated (Box 2, Folder 229)
  - John Weber, undated (Box 2, Folder 230a)
  - Jon Leon Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 230b)
  - Joseph Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 231)
  - Joyce Theater, undated (Box 2, Folder 232)
  - Jus Du Pomme, undated (Box 2, Folder 233)
  - Just Above Midtown/Downtown, undated (Box 2, Folder 234)
  - Kamikaze, undated (Box 2, Folder 235)
  - Kathryn Markel Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 236)
  - The Keith Haring Foundation, undated (Box 2, Folder 236a)
  - The Kitchen, undated (Box 2, Folder 237)
  - Kiva 309, undated (Box 2, Folder 238)
  - Korean Cultural Service, undated (Box 2, Folder 239)
  - Kornblee Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 240)
  - Kraushaar Galleries, undated (Box 2, Folder 241)
  - La Mama, undated (Box 2, Folder 242)
  - Lamb's Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 243)
  - Lamont Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 244)
  - Landmark Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 245)
  - Lapoukhine Nayduch Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 246)
  - Lapp Princess Press Ltd., undated (Box 2, Folder 247)
  - Laurence Miller Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 248)
  - Ledel, undated (Box 2, Folder 249)
  - LeFebre Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 250)
  - Leighton House, undated (Box 2, Folder 251)
  - Leila Taghinia-Milani, undated (Box 2, Folder 252)
  - Lenox Art Center, undated (Box 2, Folder 253)
  - Leo Castelli Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 254)
  - Lerner-Heller, undated (Box 2, Folder 255)
  - Leslie Lohman Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 256)
  - Light, undated (Box 2, Folder 257)
  - The Light Factory, undated (Box 2, Folder 258)
  - Liliane and Michael Durand-Dessert, undated (Box 2, Folder 259)
  - Limbo Lounge, undated (Box 2, Folder 260)
  - Limelight, undated (Box 2, Folder 261)
  - Lincoln Center Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 262)
  - Lolas-Jackson Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 263)
  - Louis K. Meisel Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 264)
  - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, undated (Box 2, Folder 265)
  - Luciaen Goldschmidt, Inc., undated (Box 2, Folder 266)
  - Madison Square Garden, undated (Box 2, Folder 267)
  - Manatus, undated (Box 2, Folder 268)
  - Manhattan Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 269)
  - Manhattan Center Stage, undated (Box 2, Folder 270)
  - Manhattan Performing Ensemble, undated (Box 2, Folder 271)
  - Margarete Roeder Fine Arts, undated (Box 2, Folder 272)
  - Margo Leavin, undated (Box 2, Folder 273)
  - Marianne Deson Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 274)
  - Marie Pellicone Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 275)
  - Marisa del Re Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 276)
  - Marlborough Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 277)
  - Marleen Pennison and Dancers, undated (Box 2, Folder 278)
  - Martin Diamond, undated (Box 2, Folder 279)
  - Mary Boone, undated (Box 2, Folder 280)
  - Mary Ryan Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 281)
  - Mary-Anne Martin, undated (Box 2, Folder 282)
  - Marcel Broodthaers, undated (Box 2, Folder 283)
  - Marcuse Pfeier Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 284)
  - Mary Mount Manhattan Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 285)
  - Master Eagle Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 286)
  - Max Hutchinson Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 287)
  - Max Protetch, undated (Box 2, Folder 288)
  - Maxwell's, undated (Box 2, Folder 288a)
  - Metro, undated (Box 2, Folder 289)
  - Metro Pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 290)
  - Metropolitain Museum of Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 291)
  - Michael Todd Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 292)
  - Middle Collegiate Church, undated (Box 2, Folder 293)
  - Millennium Film Workshop, undated (Box 2, Folder 294)
  - Minetta Lane Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 295)
  - Modern Girls, undated (Box 2, Folder 296)
  - Modern Times Theater, undated (Box 2, Folder 297)
  - Monique Knowlton Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 298)
  - Montclair Art Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 299)
  - Moore College of Art Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 300)
  - Movement Research, undated (Box 2, Folder 301)
  - Municipal Art Society, undated (Box 2, Folder 302)
  - Museum of the Borough of Brooklyn at Brooklyn College, undated (Box 2, Folder 303)
  - Museum of Holography, undated (Box 2, Folder 304)
  - Museum of Modern Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 305)
  - Museum School Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 306)
  - Music-Theatre Performing Group, undated (Box 2, Folder 307)
  - Nancy Hoffman Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 308)
  - Naropa East, undated (Box 2, Folder 309)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 310)
  - National Academy of Design, undated (Box 2, Folder 311)
  - National Multiple Sclerosis Society, undated (Box 2, Folder 312)
  - Neither Nor, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 312a)
  - Neuberger Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 313)
  - New Line Cinema, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 313a)
  - The New Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 314)
  - The New School Associates, undated (Box 2, Folder 315)
  - The New Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 316)
  - New Vic Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 317)
  - New World Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 318)
  - New York Actors Ensemble, undated (Box 2, Folder 319)
  - New York Aquarium, undated (Box 2, Folder 320)
  - New York Studio, undated (Box 2, Folder 321)
  - New York Theatre Workshop, undated (Box 2, Folder 322)
  - New York University Graduate School of Business Administration, undated (Box 2, Folder 323)
  - Newark Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 324)
  - Newfoundland Theater, undated (Box 2, Folder 325)
  - Nikon House, undated (Box 2, Folder 326)
  - Nina Freudenheim Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 327)
  - No Entiendes, undated (Box 2, Folder 328)
  - Noho Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 329)
  - Oakland Museum Association, undated (Box 2, Folder 330)
  - Off the Wall, undated (Box 2, Folder 331)
  - Ohio Performing Space, undated (Box 2, Folder 332)
  - Oil and Steel Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 333)
  - OK Harris, undated (Box 2, Folder 334)
  - 112 Greene St. Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 335)
  - One Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 2, Folder 336a)
  - One Penn Plaza, undated (Box 2, Folder 336b)
  - One Sheridan Square, undated (Box 2, Folder 337)
  - 1050 6th Avenue (Keith Haring and Kenny Scharf's Home), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 337a)
  - Organization of Independent Artists, undated (Box 2, Folder 338)
  - Oscarsson Hood Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 339)
  - P.P.O.W, undated (Box 2, Folder 340)
  - Pace Downtown Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 341)
  - Pace Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 342)
  - Pace/MacGill, undated (Box 2, Folder 343)
  - The Palace, undated (Box 2, Folder 344)
  - Palladium, undated (Box 2, Folder 345)
  - Pam Alder Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 346)
  - Pan Arts, undated (Box 2, Folder 347)
  - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre Inc., undated (Box 2, Folder 348)
  - Park Avenue Atrium, undated (Box 2, Folder 349)
  - Parrish Art Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 350)
  - Parsons Exhibition Center, undated (Box 2, Folder 351)
  - Partisan Gallery, undated (Box 2, Folder 352)
  - Paula Cooper, undated (Box 2, Folder 353)
  - Performing Garage, undated (Box 2, Folder 354)
  - Performing Space 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 355)
  - Performing Space 122, undated (Box 3, Folder 356a)
  - Performing Space 122, undated (Box 3, Folder 356b)
  - Performing Space 122, undated (Box 3, Folder 356c)
  - Performing Space 122, undated (Box 3, Folder 356)
  - Performing Space 122, undated (Box 3, Folder 356e)
  - Performing Space 122, undated (Box 3, Folder 356)
  - Performing Space 122, undated (Box 3, Folder 356g)
  - Perry Street Theatre, undated (Box 3, Folder 357)
  - Peter Noser Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 358)
  - Petersberg Press, undated (Box 3, Folder 359)
  - Phoenix Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 360)
  - The Photo Center Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 361)
  - A Photographers Place, undated (Box 3, Folder 362)
  - Photographers Unlimited, undated (Box 3, Folder 363)
  - Phyllis Kind Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 364)
  - Phyllis Weil and Co., undated (Box 3, Folder 365)